buymyplaylist.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy policy

Privacy policy
Last Revised: January 10, 2012
BuyMyPlaylist.com (the “Website” or “BMP”) is a partnership project operated by Znak Inc., a
corporation registered in the State of Delaware, Reg. Nr. 4496595; the USA EIN 27-0403537.
At BMP, we value privacy and want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. This
Policy regards information you provide to us or we learn from your use of this Website. It also
tells you how we may collect, use and, in some instances, share this information with others.
BMP collects:
     1) Information You Provide: You may provide BMP what is generally called "personally
        identifiable" information (such as your name, age, zip code, email address, PayPal or
        other alternative payment method information, credit card number, including Security
        code, postal mailing and billing address, and telephone numbers) if you use certain
        services or products our Platform or otherwise use the features and functionality of the
        Website.
     2) Your User ID/Avatar/Other Social Network IDs: Your User ID, personal profile picture or
        avatar and other BMP names/pseudonyms are displayed throughout the Website and
        are readily available to the public. Other people can see your personal playlists,
        comments, links to your online friends, etc. Therefore, if you disclose or otherwise
        associate your actual name with any of your BMP IDs, the public might be able to
        identify your activities on the Website. In addition, if you use BMP Friends and Followers
        features (as defined in the BMP Terms of Service), we will receive and store your
        Facebook, MySpace, Twitter and other social network user names you might list and
        activate there.
     3) Automatically Collected Information: When you access the BMP or open one of our
        emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using
        different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may
        include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique user ID, version of software
        installed, system type, your listening preferences, the content and pages that you access
        on the Website, and the dates and times that you visit the Website.
     4) Cookies : When you access the Website, we may send one or more small text files
        containing a string of alphanumeric characters — known as “cookies” — to your
        computer or other access devices. We do this to help improve your experience of the
        Website. We may use session cookies and persistent cookies or both. A session cookie
        disappears after you close your browser; a persistent cookie remains in your system and
        may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Website. But these
        “persistent” files can be removed if desired. Please review your web browser Help feature
        to learn the best way to modify your cookie settings. Please note, however, that by
        deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain
        areas or features of our site or the access will be much slower.

    5) Links & Embeddable Widget Information: We may display links to third party websites
        and/or embed widgets with your playlist and User ID on other sites. Please note that we
        cannot control and cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies of such websites.
        You should always read the privacy policy of a website to find out more about how
        personal information is collected and processed.
The Way BMP Uses:
The information that you provide or that we collect to the extent necessary to comply as a
service provider and a licensed partner of other service providers, including record companies,
distributors and author/copyright agencies as well as with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act
in the USA and other applicable local laws.
    Specifically we may use:
    1) your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as
        notifying you of major updates, for customer service purposes, and to send privacy or
        security related notices;
    2) your payment and billing information to process payments and earned/redeemed BMP
        credits, issue invoices, and to pay royalties, copyright fees and, if applicable, local sales
        and income taxes;
    3) all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of
        our Users, to improve the way the BMP works and looks, and to create new features
        and functionality;
    4) Automatically Collected information, Cookies, Links and Widget information to:
            a. automatically update the BMP application on your system;
            b. remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your
                visit or the next time you access the Website;
            c. provide customized third-party advertisements, content and information;
            d. monitor and report on the effectiveness of third-party marketing campaigns;
            e. monitor and report aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and
                pages accessed, tracks and playlists build using different catalogs, tracks and
                playlists purchased, and purchase prices; and,
            f. track your entries, submissions, and payment/credit earning records,
                membership status and activities in any promotions or other sponsored
                activities.
BMP May Disclose & Share:
    1) Automatically Collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information,
        such as IP addresses, anonymous User usage data, listening preferences, referring or
        exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, number and IDs of tracks and
        playlists accessed, number and type of purchases, purchase prices and, if applicable
        taxes and local fees) with interested third parties to process transactions and pay due

        fees and royalties and to assist those parties in understanding the usage and
        demographic patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, or
        other functionality on the Website, as specified in BMP license agreements.
    2) Some limited User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons
        to: provide website hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct
        data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist BMP in improving
        the Website and creating new services features. We contractually require that these
        parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize
        only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable
        confidentiality measures.
    3) User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action
        is necessary to comply with state and federal laws in the USA and the counties BMP is
        available, such (such as copyright and trademark law, tax laws and regulations) or
        respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the
        manner required by the requesting entity.
BMP Does not Share:
Your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or
promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any
personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly
available portion of the Website — such as when you publish contact information to complete
your profile information — becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others
without restriction.
You may decline to share your personally-identifiable information with BMP. In such case,
however, BMP might not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality
found on the Website. You may view, update, correct, or delete your user information and
preferences by accessing your Registration and Profile pages or by contacting us at
info@buymyplaylist.com
However, BMP reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is
appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; enforce our Terms of Service and
BMP licensing contracts; protect BMP from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate
and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government
enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Website; or to protect the
rights, property, or personal safety of BMP, our Users or others.
In addition, to protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your
identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. YOU
ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND
ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

Advertising and Sponsorship.
BMP allows third-party ad servers or ad networks and sponsoring organizations to serve
advertisements and sponsored links within the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad
networks and sponsorship programs may use technology to send, directly to your browser, the
advertisements that appear within the Website, and they automatically receive your IP Address
and other automatically collected information when this happens. Such third-party ad and
sponsorship servers may also use other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web
beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their
advertising/sponsorship content.
BMP does not provide your personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers
or ad networks and sponsorship programs without your consent. However, please note that if
an advertiser/sponsor asks BMP to show an advertisement/sponsorship opportunity to a
certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that offer, the advertiser or ad-
server and sponsorship organization may conclude that you fit the description of the audience
that they were trying to reach.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-parties for further information.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of such other
advertisers or programs. BMP reserves the right the add or remove third-party ad networks or
ad servers and sponsorship programs in its discretion and BMP may not at all times list such
updated ad network or ad server, sponsoring partners in this Privacy Policy.
Data Security
BMP uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve
the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant
the security of any information you transmit to BMP, and you do so at your own risk.
Once we receive your transmission of information, BMP makes commercially reasonable efforts
to ensure the security of our systems. However, this is not a guarantee that such information
may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical,
technical, or managerial safeguards.
If BMP learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so
that you can take appropriate protective steps. BMP may post a notice on the Website if a
security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive
notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you
should notify us at info@buymyplaylist.com.
Children's Privacy.

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE WEBSITE AT
ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. BMP does not knowingly collect or maintain personally
identifiable information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If BMP learns that personally-
identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on or through
the Website, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.
If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become the Website
member, please contact BMP at info@buymyplaylist.com to have that child's account
terminated and information deleted.
International Visitors.
For Users visiting the Website from other non-U.S. territories, please note that any data you
enter into the Website will be transferred outside such other non-U.S. territory for use by BMP
and its affiliates for any of the purposes described herein. In addition, because BMP operates
globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and
affiliates. By providing any data on the Website, you hereby expressly consent to:
     1)  the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with this
         policy; and
     2) the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.
In the Event of Merger, Sale or Other Change in Conrol.
In the case that BMP is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity or ever files for
bankruptcy, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the
information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other
change of control. Information BMP receives from you may be considered an asset subject to
bankruptcy.
Third Parties.
Except as expressly provided otherwise, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of
information we collect from you or that you disclose to us. If you disclose your information to
others besides BMP, whether they are users of the Website or on other sites or services,
different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them.
BMP does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy
policies of those third parties where applicable.
Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be
reflected by a "last modified" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes.

Your continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any
future revisions.
English Version Prevails
In the event that this Privacy Policy is translated into other languages and there is a discrepancy
between the two language versions, the English language version shall prevail to the extent that
such discrepancy is the result of an error in translation.
BMP Contact Information
If you have any suggestions, questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact
Znak Inc. the operator of the Website by writing to Znak Inc., c/o WWI, 3441 Silverside Rd,
Rodney Bld. 104, Wilmington DE, 19810, USA
Or send a message to info@buymyplaylist.com
We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.
